psmarketresearch.com 2019-09-02

# Privacy Policy | Prescient & Strategic (P&S) Intelligence

### Last updated: May 25, 2018

#### Our Commitment to Privacy

This privacy statement describes how Prescient & Strategic Intelligence Private Limited collects and uses the personal information you provide on our **website,**[ psmarketresearch.com](https://www.psmarketresearch.com/) It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

#### European Union General Data Protection Regulation

Prescient & Strategic Intelligence Private Limited follows the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), as laid down by the European law, to protect your rights regarding personal information.

#### Cookie Policy

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Our website uses these "cookies" to collect information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. By continuing to use of our site you consent to our use of cookies.

The legal basis for the processing of these information is that it is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests in maintaining the safe operation of our website and improving our website, as well as in learning from how users interact with our website.

#### Personal Information Gathering

We collect the following personal data from you:

#####  When you browse our website

 Technical Information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, referring/exit pages, viewed pages, and access dates

#####  When you ask for a product or service information

 Contact details such as email, last and first name, phone number, and company name

#####  When you create your account

 Contact details such as email, and last and first name

 Storage and use of personal Information

We store and use your personal information to:

#### Your Rights

#####  General guidance

You have the right to:

#####  Communications opt-out

You may also choose to not receive our newsletters or marketing communication by mailing us at support@psmarketresearch.com

#####  Information obtained from third parties

If you provide us with personal information about others, or if any third party provides us with your personal information, we will use that information only for that specific reason for which it was shared.

#### Information Sharing & Transfer

#####  General guidance

We do not rent or sell your personal information to third parties.

#####  Transfers to third parties

We hire service providers for certain services, such as customer relationship management (CRM), credit card processing, DNS, data management, web hosting, and web development. We provide our service providers with information that is necessary for them to perform these services and ensure that they, too, honor the privacy concerns of the clients.

We may disclose your personal information or content if we have a good-faith belief that disclosure is permitted by the law or is reasonably necessary to:

  *  Comply with a legal requirement or process, including, but not limited to, civil and criminal subpoenas, court orders, and other compulsory disclosures
  *  Enforce our Privacy Policy or Terms
  *  Respond to claims of violation of the rights of third parties
  *  Respond to service inquiries
  *  Protect the right, property, or safety of Prescient & Strategic Intelligence Private Limited, users, visitors, or the public

#### Protection of Children's Information

We are a general audience site and do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If we learn or have a reason to suspect that a site user is under 13 years of age, we will promptly delete that user’s account.

#### Security

We are strongly committed to protecting your information and, therefore, employ several industry standard methods for securing user information and data. However, because of the inherent data risks associated with the use of internet and cellular networks, we cannot guarantee 100% security to the users. Nonetheless, in the unlikely case of a security breach on our database, we assure to take a prompt action to address the issue.

We will retain your information for as long as it is required by us to provide you services. If you wish we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at support@psmarketresearch.com. We will retain and use your information, as necessary, to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements duly.

#### Additional Policy Information

#####  Notification of privacy statement changes

We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay informed about how we are protecting the information we collect.

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@psmarketresearch.com](mailto:support@psmarketresearch.com)
